RENE GOLDIN

Email: renegoldin1@gmail.com | Contact number: 065 941 9712 |

RSA ID: 841107 0290 086 | Address: 52 Roberts Road, Woodstock, Cape Town, South Africa

SUMMARY

Currently, I work as a Learning Technologist. Learning Technology allows me to combine my operational and ESL teaching background to build learning experiences. I have a BTech marketing degree, 5 years of ESL teaching, as well as more than a year working in the EdTech space. This has allowed me to become an adaptable team player. I enjoy continuously learning to build and contribute in my working environment, while maintaining a healthy work-life balance.

EXPERIENCES

January - June 2021 (Contract | Available 5 July)

Learning Technologist

Construct Education | Cape Town, South Africa

- Collaborate with Learning Design to deliver powerful, digital learning experiences on the Learning Management System.
- Design and develop courses using HTML and CSS styling to enhance the learning experience that aligns with clients branding.

Valenture Institute - Global Private Online High School

Cape Town, South Africa

September - Present 2020

Learning Technology Product Owner

- Manage and prioritise the product development backlog and oversee all product development deliverables.
- Set and maintain standards for all components and user journeys on the LMS.
- Collaborate with Learning Design to conceptualise new components and learning experiences in a manner that aligns with the Learning Technology team's user experience goals.

June - August 2020

Learning Technology Quality Lead

- Design, create and maintain system protocols by writing and updating department, and company-wide procedures.
- Measure and improve the quality of the Learning Technologists's work during the course upload, presentation phase, evaluation and portfolio checks processes.
- Identify opportunities to improve the quality of the Valenture Campus product on a continual basis.

April - June 2020

Learning Technologist

- Worked closely with the Learning Design Team to find the best technological solutions for present content in innovative ways'.
- Uploaded, formatted, and styled course content on the LMS.
- Supported the technical implementation of any third-party technologies.

October 2019 - March 2020

Learning Technologist Administrator

- Upload, format, and styling of course content on LMS.
- Apply the correct settings to groups, restrictions, prerequisites, deadlines, peer review and other specifications based on set criteria.

March - June 2019

Operations Administrator

(Maternity leave 3-month contract until 18 June 2019) Pedersen and Lennard | Cape Town, South Africa

- Actively implement processes to manage incoming orders and factory supply requirements to improve production output.
- Provide customer service and liaise with multiple clients.
- Manage logistics and production process of orders on Google Sheets.

October 2017 - March 2019

Executive Assistant to the Managing Director

New Media | Cape Town, South Africa

- Proactively managed schedules and tasks of the MD of a fast-paced agency.
- Efficiently prepared board reports for Media24 and stakeholders.
- Coordinated travel for MD, Food cluster and sales team.
- Supported all company departments, by loading SM content, sourcing supplies and planning company functions for 180 staff members.

April 2016 - August 2017

English Language Instructor

Sogang Language Program (SLP) Kindergarten and After-school Education | Busan, South Korea

- Interviewed and trained instructors.
- Assessed students' writing and speaking abilities.
- Taught and improved second language students' English abilities through stimulating and outcome-focused content.

Gyeonggi English Village Paju, South Korea

April 2015 - April 2016

Adult Program Coordinator & Instructor

- Developed specialised adult programmes to client's briefs.
- Managed a team of 10 instructors from the U.S, South Korea and Australia.
- Evaluated programmes through research and consultations with stakeholders, and implemented changes when needed.

October 2012 - April 2015

ESL Teacher for Adults and Young Learners

- Researched, developed and prepared interactive English lessons.
- Collaborated on curriculum development and assisted process to completion.
- Supervised and interacted with students from South Korea, Japan and Russia.
- Trained new staff members and evaluated performances.

September 2010 - August 2012

Marketing, Sales and Customer Service

World Gaia Trading and the Green Shop | Hout Bay, Cape Town, South Africa

- Generated new sales and maintained relationships with customers.
- Updated promotional material such as brochures and instore displays.
- Sourced solutions for clients and general administrative tasks.

June 2008 - January 2010

Online Content Editor

Entertainment Website WhatsOn.co.za | Cape Town, South Africa

- Compiled, updated and edited online content daily through a CMS.
- Liaised with stakeholders to coordinate weekly promotions.
- Maintained and increased the site's users and page impressions through marketing efforts.

EDUCATION

2007 Bachelor of Technology (BTech) Marketing

Cape Peninsula University of Technology I Cape Town, South Africa

2003 National Matric Certificate with Merit

Herzlia High School I Cape Town, South Africa

FURTHER DEVELOPMENT

January 2019 Learning Digital with Google

Google Programme, Digital Skills for Africa

April 2014 The Advanced Creative Writing Online Course

South African Writers College, South Africa

August 2012 **TESOL 120 Hour Certificate**

Cape Town School of English/ TESOL Training Institute, Cape Town, South Africa

- Microsoft Office and Google Suite
- South African driver's licence (Code B)
- English (Fluent) Afrikaans (Basic)
- Canvas LMS
- HTML and CSS
- Articulate Storyline and Rise 360
- Adobe Captivate

REFERENCES AVAILABLE